Postman Pat: The Movie is a family, comedy,
animation film directed by Mike Disa.
Like always, Postman Pat is happily going about his duty delivering
letters and parcels around the fictional town of Greendale.
One day, auditions for the TV talent show, "You're the One", are
held in Greendale, which Pat manages to pass.
With Pat required to be away from Greendale whilst participating in the contest,
various Patbot 3000 robots are deployed to take Pat's postal duties.
This soon turns out to be an evil plot to take over
the world, which Pat must now stop.
Postman Pat (voice), played by Stephen Mangan.
CEO (voice), played by Jim Broadbent.
Josh (voice), played by Rupert Grint.
Wilf (voice), played by David Tennant.
Postman Pat (singing voice), played by Ronan Keating.
Sara Clifton (voice), played by Susan Duerden.
Postman Pat: The Movie is a 2014 animated comedy film based on the British
television series Postman Pat by John Cunliffe and Ivor Wood.
It was directed by Mike Disa, produced by Robert Anich Cole, written by
Nicole Dubuc, with music by Rupert Gregson-Williams.
It was co-produced by Classic Media, RGH Pictures and Timeless Films.
The film stars Stephen Mangan, Jim Broadbent, Rupert Grint, David Tennant, Ronan
Keating, Susan Duerden, Sandra Teles, TJ Ramini and Peter Woodward.
It was released in the UK on 23 May 2014 by Lionsgate UK and Icon
Film Distribution respectively and in the US by Shout!
Factory, and received mixed reviews from critics.
The film grossed $8.6 million worldwide.
The tone is lighthearted.